Samurai
Ah, this summer has come again
has come, has come, has come, has come
The great battle has come, the grand Tokyo
Noya-jukuri's
In the south wind
Big chest
Chikai chest
Noya-jukuri's
Aki-sori
Pururururururu
Ah, this year too
Summer has come
Chikai Chikai
Ah, this year too
Summer has come
Chikai Chikai
Big Nami-chikai
Nami-chikui
Noya-jukuri's
In the south wind
Big butt
Chikai Chikai
Naya-jukuri's
Aki-sori
Purururururu
Ah, this year too
South wind
Chikai
Ah, this year too
Nagisa
Nagesa
Purururu
"Batsumatsu Police Officer: Ryotsu Arawaru"
Here it comes!
You're pretty fired up this morning, Ryo-san!
I'm late!
I can't believe you stopped me here.
What's with the nervousness?
Get out of the way!
No way!
Wait!
"Batsumatsu Police Officer: Ryotsu Arawaru"
Thanks, Mr. Ryo!
Hey, that's Ryo-san!
50 km/h!
60 km/h!
70 km/h!
80 km/h!
The過去メーカー is entering the 10,000 rpm red zone!
90° hang on!
This is terrible!
Oh, no!
The future is in your hands!
I did it!
I made it in time!
I'm glad that you made it!
It's not good, Ryo.
The glass broke, and the chief will be mad at me again.
Hey, Ryo.
I watered that flower every day, and it finally bloomed.
I won't forgive you if you touch it again.
He's as noisy as ever.
What? The chief hasn't come yet.
It's not like that.
You know, people who stand on people's feet
always come 30 minutes earlier.
R-Ryo!
What's wrong, Terai?
Chief!
Yes, Chief.
You're good at this.
It's my honor to leave the countryside
and spend two and a half hours on the plane.
I'm proud of you.
You can see that
in not only how three of us work,
You idiot!
You're too unreasonable.
Every day this day,
the police are slow,
so you'll find me here
and appreciate my figurative skills.
You idiot!
Even if you're a bachelor, you do the same as the children's university entrance exam.
How many exams do you have to write to get a degree?
Are you planning to get into the Guinness Book of Records?
That's why you don't have a wife.
Live your life more seriously.
There's a song like this in my favorite Suizenji Kiyoko's song.
One step a day, three steps in three days,
three steps forward, two steps back.
This is it!
Here, here, here!
Suizenji Kiyoko, the chief's box!
That's it, that's it!
Three steps forward, two steps back.
One step forward, two steps back.
I was a fool to teach you how to be modest about life.
My head hurts.
It's finally over.
I was stupid for the second time.
You know,
I remember one stupid thing.
Chief!
Did you forget something?
That's right.
Today was my payday.
I don't want to do it to you, but I can't help it.
Listen, Ryozu.
Don't use it right away because you have money.
Think about the future.
Use it in a planned manner.
Yes.
Oh, Ryozu.
Just play fishing and lead the ship and that's that.
Right.
Let's go in and find a new machine.
Here, Ryozu.
Yeah, that's good.
You're in the shoes and excited,
so you can cooling it down quickly.
Yeah.
A machine running here?
Rocco-kun, where did you get that from?
I'm here to get your bonus.
Ugh! Everyone at the shopping street is here!
Crap! If this keeps up...
Run!
Corona!
C-Captain!
Derai! Hold both of their legs!
Y-Yes!
Let go! Let go!
Derai! You're not getting away!
Now, everyone, please take him away!
Let go!
It's not bad, Ryo.
Game software and Plumdive, 38,000 yen.
I'll take it.
Ramen is 21,000 yen.
Beer and whiskey, 28,000 yen.
Oh, it's a bit too much.
Beer is 18,000 yen.
Zurizao is 3,000 yen.
Seriously?
What?
3,000 yen.
Bye!
150 yen.
That's all for this month?
You're so selfish.
That's why I said you had to live a healthy life.
Captain!
Don't make a fool of yourself!
Be a man and live a month, that's all.
No!
Don't lend money to Ryo, Derai or Reiko.
I have a house loan to pay for my house.
It's fine.
You can live with just that.
Yeah, don't be so sweet.
I'll pay you back for both.
Captain.
Don't say that.
50,000 yen.
No, 30,000 yen is fine.
Then 20,000 yen.
10,000 yen.
At least 1,000 yen.
No!
Keiji!
I won't cry to anyone anymore.
If you're going to cry to such cold people,
you'd better die!
You said it.
Don't forget what you said.
I'm not sure you'll be able to make it anyway.
I'm going to send you a happy,
meaningful life for 150 yen!
Kids' fights, aren't they?
Yeah.
"I'm dying to be a full-time worker!"
My watch is gone.
That was a good name.
There's no Reiko.
How about we have a lunch together?
It hurts!
Ryo-chan, you should have died from the fire.
Who said that?
Damn! I was reading the pattern.
Damn! Give me your bed!
No! This is mine!
Ryo-chan, you're stealing other people's things.
Shut up! The name is written on the rice grain!
Give it to me!
Ryo-chan, stop it!
No!
Ryo-chan!
This is what you get for being a good boy!
You're amazing when it comes to the rice grain.
Damn!
Why am I so hungry, eh?
Do they have any food?
Oh, I found something.
I found this "Kagami Mochi".
Alright. This must contain something edible.
Hmm...
I'll have some ponzu.
Ah, too much.
That's too much. This is too sour.
I'll add salt and add it to my mouth.
I added too much of anything.
I'll add sugar.
Well, it's fine. It's this much.
I'll season it with tonkatsu sauce.
The mass-produced hot pot is complete!
The Shogatsu Kagami mochi is left.
What? Isn't that the one that got really moldy?
No, it's not.
You're stupid.
Mushrooms are also a kind of hair.
It has a lot of aji-sai leaves.
It's a perfect balance of nutrition.
Eating aji-sai leaves?
It's called aji-sai, so it's got a good taste.
The color is not good.
Ryo! That's Reiko's...
Color is important in cooking.
Thank you for the meal!
Ryo?
What are you doing?
I told you not to touch it again!
You bastard!
Damn it.
Leave some for me, you jerk.
I'm hungry.
What's this?
There!
Isn't that Junpei and Kappei from the tofu shop?
Junpei, you're the best!
You can do it, Junpei!
No, no, no, no.
You're doing a good job, sir.
You're quite good at cooking.
The octopus looks delicious.
Junpei, how about you compete with me?
With Ryo?
That's right.
We'll have a one-on-one game.
If I win, you'll get this octopus.
What if Ryo loses?
You'll get your favorite stuff,
and I'll give you this.
What?
You're playing?
What do you say?
Are you ready, Junpei?
Yes.
Let's see who wins the first round of the game!
It's busy.
Oh, Ryo.
I won!
With a score of one million and nine hundred and eighty points,
you're pretty good.
You're pretty good.
It's my turn next.
Start!
Triss-sart!
Kurenai Idareuchi!
I'm screwed!
Aimei Uchi!
Kurenai Uchi!
I won!
Awesome!
What do you think?
I lost.
You should have stopped, Big Brother.
As promised, I'll take the Takoyaki.
Oh no!
Huh?
Junpei!
You bastard!
Are you ok?
Ryo!
Hey!
This is bad!
Wait!
Stop!
It's dangerous!
What?
Uraaaaaaaaaaa!
The bicycle is going to get tired...
Ultra Power Turbo On!
Yosu!
Yata! They are chasing me with bicycles!
I'm not going to let you catch me.
I'll catch you if you let me.
Are you serious?
I'm not letting you get away!
You bastard!
Alright, let's get this over with!
Missile Jump!
Damn it! It's a shortcut!
What are you doing, Ryo-san?
Zuma, the mine is being destroyed!
Oh no!
Missile Jump!
Get back here!
I'm on the boat!
They're still after us! Hurry up!
They're so stubborn!
Don't underestimate me!
They're still after us at 80km/h!
Hurry up!
Move, you idiot!
Looks like he finally gave up.
No way!
Wait, you idiot!
He's a monster!
No way!
He's not following us!
Well done, Ken-chan.
That's it! The exit!
Take this!
No!
Then we've held him captive.
Brilliant.
You bastard!
Yes?
Sorry, I won't do it again.
Give me back my takoyaki!
My takoyaki! Give me back my takoyaki!
You did it, Ryo.
It's been 8 years since I've been a criminal, congratulations.
Congratulations.
Well, I was a criminal for a while, but I've been a criminal for a while.
A criminal is a criminal, right?
You don't look like one, Ryo.
Ryo!
Hey, Junpei.
Are you done with your legs?
That's a big deal!
Ryo, I'm sure you'll win the game next time.
Yeah, yeah.
You should practice hard, Junpei.
Come to think of it, I haven't eaten anything yet.
Oh, yeah.
That driver was a traffic criminal with a sign.
This is probably a special award, a gold medal.
A gold medal?
Yay!
I'll be saved this month!
Ryo, are you there?
Uh-oh.
Yes!
Here is the great police officer of Kameari, Ryo Kankichi, who arrested the criminal Atene-han.
You're going to pay me a gold medal, right?
You idiot!
Look outside!
Ryo!
I heard you caused trouble for your neighbors again.
You'll be fined from next month's salary!
N-no!
Please forgive me, I'm so sorry!
Next time on Kameari Kouen-mai
wrath to the central police
The police officer came to Kameari Park,
the new police officer is the only son of Nakagawa family.
How can the police officer be a chauffeur in this cattle market?
Next time, the new policemen from the sky, welcome
Thank you for watching!
Please smile, you're not bad
Please smile, you're still the same
Always smile
Because a woman in dark clothes isn't pretty
I should smile right away
Please smile, you're not bad
Because a woman in dark clothes isn't pretty
I should smile right away